Two years have passed since
the war between the Navy,
the Seven Warlords, and
the Whitebeard Alliance,
but its repercussions are still
felt throughout the world.
This is the deserted island of
Ruskina, northwest of Amazon Lily.
Yeah, I'm coming
Time really sneaks up on you, huh?
Two years already
Hey!
Find someone else to eat.
She's my friend.
Luffy, the ship is all ready to sail.
Give the word, and we'll be off.
Got it. Thanks.
I should have known.
He's the boss of the whole island now.
Yeah, it's kind of a shame.
I was planning on eating these guys,
but since we're friends now,
that would be weird, huh?
They still look pretty yummy, though.
Don't you worry about food.
I have all of your favorites
ready and waiting on the ship.
Since I'm so thoughtful,
I wouldn't blame you if you
wanted to get married right away.
I'll pass on the marriage,
but thanks for the food.
Cold as ever and yet my heart is on fire!
I heard that Rayleigh left
a hole six months ago.
I assume he's waiting for
you back on Sabaori now.
Yeah, I learned the basics
a little ahead of schedule.
All that's left is to say bye
to my friends here, I guess.
So long, you guys.
Time to go!
Gold Roger, the king of the pirates,
attained every treasure
that the world had to offer.
Smiling, even as he stood upon the scaffold,
he issued a challenge to the world.
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
Now those who dare to dream, hoist their
flags and sail into the Great Pirate Era!
Jump start!
If you want to go to the world,
You need your own tag?
That's what I need!
I'm not sure how it is.
I'm just the only thing I'm doing.
I'm not sure how you are?
I'm not sure how it is.
but I don't know how it is.
Did you hear?
They relocated Navy HQ.
Oh?
Did they now? Yeah.
They traded locations
with a branch called G1.
That moved them to the
other side of the red line.
Their new fleet admiral's a lot
more cocky than Sengoku was.
Moved right into the
Four Emperors' territory.
He's not afraid to stare down the
toughest pirates in the world.
On the upside, that keeps
him out of our business.
But on the downside,
we've got a lot more
criminals running around
and nobody to stop them
when things get ugly.
Oh.
It did seem like there were an awful
lot of thugs compared to two years ago.
Hey, did you catch this?
Yeah, it's a shocker, huh?
I had to do a double take, but it looks
like the Straw Hats are back after all.
I never heard word of
them dying or anything,
but two years is a long time for
anyone to just disappear like that.
Either way, looks like they're
recruiting some new members.
This is a good place for it.
If you made it here, that means you
survived the first half of the Grand Line,
and those guys keep pouring in.
His crew's pretty small.
Makes sense that he'd want to pick up
some more before heading to the New World.
That sounds like fun to me.
I'd make a great Straw Hat, right?
That chance.
There's guys with 100 million berry
bounties all over the place here.
What would they want
with a chump like you?
That's cruel, man.
Oh, come on, bro.
There's got to be something you can do.
Like what?
We're sold out.
This is the Soul King World Tour.
You can't waltz up and buy tickets
when the show is about to start.
This is the final
concert of the tour, too.
Can't you hear them?
The crowd is ready to rock!
Hey, manager.
Let's make this the greatest
show of my afterlife.
Well, of course, of course.
Now would be the time.
Your TDs are at the height of their sales.
In fact, we just broke a million.
You certainly earned your
title as the king of soul.
Just listen to those
fans chanting your name?
I can dig it, boss man!
But one thing before the concert.
I got something heavy to lay on you.
I'm all ears, friend.
Come
on, baby!
I love you down to my own bone.
I'm gonna ring a sorry neck bone.
How selfish can he be?
Hey, grab me a transponder, snail.
I'm not gonna let you
walk all over me, Brooke.
Today is a reunion, an
anniversary, and a celebration!
I'm so...
Women!
Real women!
No stubble, no hairy legs, no giant chins,
just honest-to-goodness beautiful girls!
How I've longed for your
delicate features your
soft skin to hear the
intoxicating words resting
on your sweet lips it
looks like this is farewell
i hate to part but
we'll meet again someday
I hope not thanks for the ride
and say hi to Eva but go away
what's up ladies i'm fresh out
of I'm looking for a good time!
Like they say, if a boy picks on a
girl, that means he has a crush on her.
Oh, I know.
Happens to me all the time.
Love is patient, Sanji! We'll wait!
We know you'll come back!
I'm on my way, Nami Swan!
Robin, my love!
What's the matter?
Can't read?
Or are you just stupid?
I know preschoolers with
higher bounties than that.
How about you check that poster again?
If your bounty is under 70
million, then we don't want you.
Phil, why don't you take your
weak ass back to pirate daycare?
If that's all you're worth, it's
a wonder you made it this far.
Bastard!
Now scram!
I'm the thun of Dragon the Revolutionary.
I ain't got time for this.
We're the chosen ones, boyo.
No chumps are gonna run with this crew.
We're in a league of our own.
If you can't get with us, you
better get the hell out of our way.
Too late.
That's rough.
This real hat is fierce.
Of course he is.
He's a legend.
What's the count, Franky?
How many recruits we got?
About a hundred last time I checked.
Three whole crews joined up
along with ten guys running solo.
They've got some nice bounties, too.
I know two of them.
A pair of high-profile rookies
joined at the same time.
Wet-haired caribou and
blood-splattered coribou.
They love killing Marines.
Brothers and captains worth
$210 million and $190 million.
Now they answer to us.
And there's more where they came from.
Hey, bring another round.
Yes, sir.
Better make it quick.
I see you sitting alone over there, Missy.
If you want to have a good time,
why don't you party with us?
She's a real looker, ain't she?
I'll pass.
I'm here waiting for a friend.
This is about to get ugly.
Listen, I would not turn that man down.
You realize that Straw Hat Luffy, right?
Yeah,
the same Straw Hat that
burst into Marineford
and went head-to-head
with the Navy Admirals.
He's nuts!
Waiting for a friend?
Captain Luffy is a star, baby!
Your friend would probably
piss his pants if he saw him.
Come drink with some real men.
I'm only gonna say this once.
You can take your offer and shove it,
because I'm way out of your league.
What?
You understand, Mr...
whoever you are?
You don't know me?
I'm Straw Hat Luffy, you Wind.
Hey, come on, say you're sorry. Hurry!
Huh?
Nobody disrespects me.
Let me handle this.
Har har.
You think you're real cute, don't you?
I'll make this super simple, okay?
Either you come drink with
Captain Luffy, or you die.
For your info, I have a bounty myself.
I'm the Straw Hat's navigator, Nami.
You scared yet?
Special attack, green star?
Devil!
Huh?
Whoa, what the hell?
It doesn't save me!
It's like a sale coming from me!
Giant plant?
Where'd that come from?
Hey there, beautiful.
Can I buy you a drink?
Look at you! Those muscles! And that hair!
You tough guy!
You look great!
I missed you! Thanks!
Your hair looks nice, too!
That hot girl was waiting
for that pencil-nosed geek.
What does he have to week out?
New special move, huh?
Yeah, they come from
seeds called Pop Greens.
Needless to say, I wasn't just sitting
around on my tail these past two years.
It's a new me.
I'm not part of the weakling trio
with you and Chopper anymore.
That means no more running and hiding.
I'm a real warrior now.
Uh, hey, dude, if you did this, could you
undo it? What the? Sniper King? But how?
Usok, forget about them.
Let's get out of here.
There's something we need to talk about.
You stop right there. Luffy? Ignore him.
Ma 'am, you haven't paid your tab yet.
Take the change.
Crap, they're making fools of us.
Get them down now.
Son of a...
Um, guys, what are those
weird bubble things?
I have a feelin' this
ain't gonna be pretty.
What the hell's going on here?
Yeah, so I picked up some
new special moves myself.
You show off!
Can't you let me be cool for once?
Who do they think they are?
Hunt those bastards down and murder him.
I have a report, sir,
from Sabo Odi Archipelago.
What?
You say the Straw Hats are back?
Yes, sir.
Word is that they're recruiting new crew
members before they head to the new world.
Had a feeling Straw Hat was still alive.
Inform headquarters of this immediately.
Send in as many backup
units as we can spare
and begin a search of the
entire archipelago. Sir!
I think I shook them off.
Brooke is holding a concert, and the
Straw Hats are looking for new recruits?
Goodness, I've been gone for too long.
Soul King does have a
nice ring to it, though!
You're kidding me!
You're saying this swordsman who barely
knows left from right got here first?
Well, what do you know?
Maybe he learned how to read
a map while he was training.
After him came Franky
about ten days ago now.
But he headed back out to go see
if your ship was doing all right.
I hope that means the
Sunny is in good shape.
Of course, there isn't
a single scratch on it.
We finished the coding, too.
That's good to hear.
Just make sure you give
credit where credit's due.
Even if you don't, there's
no shame in a wound of honor.
It's time for some R &R!
Who knew you'd be so
dedicated to the cause?
Your stubbornness came in handy.
You mean my looks?
Don't mention it, I owe you one anyway.
Come rain or shine, it changed nothing.
Dangerous pirates from all
over came to take that ship.
Didn't matter how bad I was hurt,
I defended it day after day.
Cause I knew all these
bruises would be worth it.
You're so amazing, sir.
Pirates messed you up?
Come on, what's the
real story here, Devil?
Don't be impatient.
I'm trying to build up the
suspense here, you know.
You see, what happened
was the Navy showed up.
The third member of your
crew to arrive was Nami.
Nami!
That's great, is she still here?
She decided to kill time by
getting some shopping done.
Come on, don't you want to
hear the rest of my story?
The fourth one to arrive was Usopp
three days ago, who also went into town,
followed by Chopper,
who showed up yesterday.
Brooks made it, too.
He's putting on a concert
for the islanders today.
No way.
You're the last to stop by,
which makes seven in total.
Not that I expected any less,
but almost the entire crew
has made it back in good time.
That's right.
Only Nico, Robin, and Luffy remain.
Getting to this island
in the first place is
a difficult task for
any crew to accomplish.
And yet, you've made it twice.
What can I say?
You must be eager to see each other again.
Yeah.
And by the way, I still can't believe
you trained Luffy while we were gone.
He must be crazy strong now.
He's been on his own
these last six months.
I can't wait to see how
his skills have developed.
Now that you...
mention it...
I can't wait to see how Nami's
developed, if you know what I'm saying!
I should have expected that.
Hey, guys!
What's the matter?
Come on, talk to me!
I thought you'd be more excited to
see me, but you're acting weird.
From the looks of things, you've all
changed a lot over these last two years.
But I mean, we're still friends,
so why are you ignoring me?
You, man, it's not leaving.
Oh, you must be shy because
of how much I've changed, too.
And if you ask me, that furball knows
a little too much about us Straw Hats,
if you know what I mean.
Yeah, I do.
And you gotta wonder why that is.
Maybe we can find the answer here.
No, it can't be!
That's the real deal, cotton
candy-loving Tony Tony Chopper!
The pet's coming home.
So we all look a little
different than we used to.
Who cares?
He must have been abandoned
on this island when they
died and he's been living
in the wild ever since.
And now he's following
us around because he
thinks his masters have
finally come back for him.
We should ditch the mutt
and take him instead.
If we have their real pet, no one will
ever doubt we're the Straw Heads again.
Sounds good.
What's he eat?
Probably cotton candy.
We ain't got none of that.
Get it!
We don't need you no more!
Come here, boy. You hungry?
Yum, right?
You're kind of freaking me out!
Now!
Robin!
Hey! Stop! Come back!
Who were those creeps? Oh, no!
This is a real emergency!
What are we gonna do now?
I guess we should tell
Captain Luffy, right?
Maybe he knows how to handle this mess.
Wait!
I didn't know Luffy was
back on the island already!
You're right, and we'll have new
recruits by now. That's great!
With the extra might,
we'll save Robin for sure!
Let's go get our friend back!
Calling from Sabaori!
We've secured Nico Robin!
We've also caught some fox thing
that won't stop biting her head!
It's been a while.
Surely the others have
made it back by now.
Hey!
Are you all right?
Hey, why did he do that?
He just shot her out of the
blue Come on, we'll get a doctor
You what is wrong with you?
She didn't do a damn
thing to deserve that. Uh,
I thought you were
someone else I said sorry,
so here's the deal I'm looking for some
punks who crossed me and made a run for it a
red-haired woman and
a guy with a long nose
So you just shot her
That's normal for you?
This won't end well.
Straw Hat's a monster.
Eh?
You wanna fight about it?
Cause I got plenty more bullets.
Your choice, pal.
Don't blame me.
Blame your nose.
Hey!
We'll get some help!
Stay with me!
Find those punks now,
or I'll shoot you too!
We got a reputation to uphold here!
We gotta show this place who's boss!
Oops.
Didn't see you there.
Sorry about that. See ya.
That guy's insane.
Either that or he doesn't
know who Strawhide is.
He's a dead man either way.
Get back here!
There in the distance
is Sabo Odi Archipelago.
Forgive me, Luffy, but we will
have to say our goodbyes here.
We cannot let anyone discover
the nature of our relationship.
I've prepared a disguise for you.
Are you kidding?
I can't pull that look off.
Perhaps, but I would still feel more
at ease if you took it. All right.
You must be careful.
Keep your face hidden at all times.
The world may believe you've
been dead these last two years,
but that won't stop anyone from recognizing
you the first time you get into trouble.
So if you ever want to set sail
again, you'll take my advice to heart.
Thanks. I'll try. You're welcome.
Now, for supplies, I've loaded your
backpack with 50 changes of clothes,
1,000 lunches, handkerchiefs, and tissues.
You'll also find three years' worth of
water, snacks, and bugbite ointment.
There's also five years'
worth of towels, toothbrushes,
plenty of soaps, hand creams,
and lots of silverware.
That is entirely too much!
Well, I hope you can
find all your friends.
Thanks again for getting me
here and all the other stuff.
We were more than happy to help you.
Your most difficult trials
may still be ahead of you.
I hear that Sabo Odi has
become a den of crime.
And because of that,
the Navy has been keeping a tight watch
over the goings-on there as late, my boy.
So be sure to take extra care.
Right.
If you ever need assistance,
the full force of the
Kuja pirates will come
rushing to your aid at a moment's notice.
Please don't hesitate to call on us.
Also, would you be
willing to do me a favor?
Yeah, maybe.
As long as it's not getting married.
No, no.
All I ask is that when you leave,
you do so without saying farewell.
That all?
I've never said that to
anyone before, so sure.
Besides, I want to see you again.
Alright, I'm out of here!
Bye, hurry!
You take care!
Oh, my.
He wants to see me again.
That's practically a proposal.
No, it's not.
Hancock told me I got to stay
out of trouble and lay low.
I don't want to fight this guy.
Hey, dummy.
Did you run into me on purpose?
Oh, no.
He's going to kill that poor guy.
PIANO PLAYS
Hi, Sunny.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I hope you aren't lonely.
You're as lovely as ever.
Huh?
Ow!
Now who is that gorgeous lady?
It's Robin, of course,
our super archaeologist!
Boy, did I miss you!
You haven't changed a bit, Franky.
Is that a joke, sister?
I'm a brand new man!
No, I'm more than a man.
I'm the stuff dreams are made of.
Gaze upon this fantastic transformation,
the likes of which this
world has never seen!
Yeah, baby!
I'm beyond human comprehension!
Fair enough.
Though I might argue that you've been
that way for quite some time now.
Huh?
So I'm not just a freak,
I'm a super freak?
Ha ha, you're gonna make me blush!
This is the coating, I take it?
It's like jelly.
Yep, took a little longer than we
expected, but Rayleigh did his part.
Bottom of the sea, here we come!
After everyone gets back, of course.
Speaking of which, I saw
Rayleigh at the bar. Oh, yeah?
What number were you?
Who are we missing?
I was number eight.
So the only one left is him.
Oofy.
Well, I'm sure our captain
will show up soon enough.
Ship's ready whenever he is.
New weapon's ready, too.
That sounds just splendid.
By the way, where's everyone else, Issie?
Usopp and Sanji stopped by here earlier.
Usopp's picking up some fuel for the trip.
Sanji's getting groceries,
of course. I see.
I ran into something
interesting on the way over.
Have you seen these?
It's for a concert today.
He's calling himself Soul King.
Yeah, there's a story behind that.
He's big news now.
They're selling his
TDs all over the place.
He's left the darkness far behind.
He rose up from those foggy seas
and now he's a shining star.
His fans raise his name to the
heavens if you'll pardon my poetry.
He didn't say anything about this to me.
But he's making a lot of
people happy with his music.
He might not want to be a pirate anymore?
It's no mystery, just rock with me.
And you'll see why I'm the king.
It is in your skeleton, cause
calcium is all that you need.
So dish that fat and protein, make your
body mean and lean. Got milk? Got milk?
Got milk?
My soul is flowing out of my head.
So what are you gonna say for yourself?
You can't tell me you didn't know
who I was when you crashed into me.
Why do it?
Were you just trying to
make a fool out of me?
Cause if so, I don't like
being shown up in public.
After all, I have a reputation and a
400 million buried bounty to uphold.
But you can make it up to me, by kneeling.
Beg for your life and
I might feel generous.
Yo!
Fisherman, you in?
Looking for some good stock at a
low price. Huh? It's the place?
Hey, you run this shack.
What's the matter?
It's something awful.
That green-haired man's gone.
Aw, crap.
All right, old man, spill it.
I can't believe this has happened to me.
Well, you see, uh...
Hey, Gramps.
I was looking to do some fishing.
Huh?
No offense, young man, but I wouldn't
exactly beg you as the fishing type.
Normally, you'd be right.
I'm supposed to be meeting
some friends on this island,
but they haven't made it yet.
So I'm bored out of my skull.
So I need something to keep
me entertained while I wait.
You think you can help
me out or not? Sure.
I'll finish getting
everything we need ready
and then meet you on my
boat right over there.
And that's all I said to him.
To be clear, did this guy have three
swords and a belly warmer? Yes, he did.
And he had a deep scar on his eye, too.
How'd you know?
Scars knew.
Is this him?
Yeah.
He said he'd been waiting
on some friends to show.
That must be you.
Well, I wouldn't go that far.
You see, I told him to
wait on my fishing boat?
While I was getting ready, and
I pointed right at the thing.
But when I came outside,
he'd made a huge mistake. No!
Young man!
You've got it wrong!
You're on a pirate ship! No, men.
It's time we set sail for the
new world we've been dreaming of.
The wait is over!
Come on, please!
You have to wake up!
You've got on the pirate ship!
Since they went underwater, I guess
they were headed to Fishman Island.
That idiot.
Should have known him showing up
here first was too good to be true.
Wouldn't be Zoro if he
didn't get lost somewhere.
Aren't you worried at all?
They might kill him on that ship.
It's fine.
Don't get worked up.
This is pretty standard fare, actually.
Better than usual, even, since we
know where he's going for once.
Now, would you mind selling
me some fish already?
I don't think you understand.
Whoa! See that?
Huh?
Look at the waves!
Something's coming up!
But what?!
It must be huge!
That's a galleon ship!
He must have had poor coating and
was crushed under the water pressure.
No, it has to be the work of Sea Kings.
But it looks like it's been cut
in half, like someone attacked it.
No way.
Just think for a second.
Who in the world could do that?
Damn you.
Tell me why.
How could you just ruin our dreams
of reaching the new world like this?
Call it a twist of fate.
That's what brought this
plague upon your ship.
And there's no one for you
to blame but yourselves.
Are you kidding me?
Who the heck is that guy?
A great back already.
And he's still a pain in the ass.
That wasn't my ride.